http://www.feltbicycles.com/pages/terms-conditions

TERMS & CONDITIONS, COPYRIGHT NOTICE, AND PRIVACY POLICY
Thank you for visiting the Felt Bicycles ("FELT") web site.   We hope you find your experience in visiting the web site to be informative, helpful, and entertaining.  In order to provide an optimal experience, we provide our privacy policy and copyright notice below.
AGREEMENT
By visiting our website, you are agreeing to the terms and conditions of our Copyright notice and Privacy Policy.   If you do not agree to the terms stated herein, you should not use the FELT web site.
COPYRIGHT NOTICE
©Copyright 2006-13 Felt Racing, LLC & Felt GmbH.   All Rights Reserved.   This copyright notice applies to the entire contents of this website.
All content on this website is the sole property of FELT and is protected under US and International copyright laws.   FELT reserves all rights to the content contained herein.
The content of this website or any Internet site owned, operated, licensed, or controlled by FELT may be viewed or downloaded for the user's personal, noncommercial use only.   Even for personal downloads, you may not modify the materials nor use the materials in a manner that suggests an association with any of our products, services, or brands.   The content herein, including trademarks, service marks, written text, html or other code, images, animations, digital photographs, or other content accessible on this site, should not be reproduced, copied, distributed, posted, or used in any other way without the express written permission of FELT.   The use of any FELT material on any other Web site or computer environment is prohibited.   You may link to material on our website only with our prior written consent.
CONTENT
THE MATERIALS ON THIS WEBSITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED.   TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, WE DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.   WE DO NOT WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE MATERIALS WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT ANY FELT SITE OR THE SERVERS THAT MAKE SUCH MATERIALS AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.   YOU ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR, OR CORRECTION.   APPLICABLE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.   UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NEGLIGENCE, SHALL WE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM THE USE OF, OR THE INABILITY TO USE, THE   FELT WEBSITE OR MATERIALS OR FUNCTIONS ON ANY SUCH SITE, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.   APPLICABLE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY OR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.   IN NO EVENT SHALL OUR TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES, AND CAUSES OF ACTION WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE EXCEED THE AMOUNT PAID BY YOU, IF ANY, OR $100 (WHICHEVER IS LESS) FOR ACCESSING OR PARTICIPATING IN ANY ACTIVITY RELATED TO THE FELT WEBSITE SITE.
Articles may be published on this website by other authors are also subject to the foregoing limitations.   The actions and ideas presented in these articles do not necessarily represent the opinions or recommendations of Felt.   Felt does not guarantee the accuracy of any information contained in these articles.   Felt is not responsible for any errors or omissions or for the results obtained from the use of information in these articles, nor shall Felt be liable or responsible to any person or entity for any loss or damage caused, or alleged to have been caused, directly or indirectly by the information or ideas referenced or suggested on this site.
PRIVACY POLICY
At FELT, we respect your privacy and will take reasonable steps to assure the protection of your privacy.   Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.   As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit, and you do so at your own risk.   Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.   You can report network abuse and any risk of security violations to us by emailing via our CONTACT US page.   This website may contain links to other sites.   Please be aware that we are not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and that this Privacy Policy applies solely to the information which we collect through this website.   We encourage you to ensure that you read the privacy statements of all the destination sites which you visit.
INFORMATION COLLECTED
FELT will collect information voluntarily from you through the normal course of using the web site.   In addition to information that you enter into forms on the web site, other information is gathered under normal web practices in order to optimize your browsing experience.
The information collected will include anonymous and user-identifiable data.   User-identifiable data includes data, which the user enters into forms on the web site, or entered into affiliate web sites, which link to our web site.   This may also include cookies or other web technologies, which allow the user's computer to communicate with our web servers to assure continuity of web page flow and customization of content to the user.   Anonymous data may include web site logs, referral information, data from cookies, or other means.
Your browser software utilizes a feature known as "cookies" Cookies tell us nothing about you personally unless you specifically give us additional information.   If enabled through your browser, cookies may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of the FELT Websites.
Any personal information that you volunteer will be maintained within FELT's control and will not be sold to or shared with other parties not affiliated with FELT.   FELT reserves the right to use the personal information that you provide to enable us to respond to your communications and/or requests, to provide our web site designers with useful information for developing new features and services, to tailor your web browsing experience to match your preferences.
Your personal information will not be sold to or shared with third parties not associated with FELT without your express permission.   When you provide your personal information, you will be given the option to "opt-in", which requires action on your part to provide permission.   Your information may be provided to third parties if you "opt-in", allowing us to share the information.   From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice.   If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.   If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically
EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS
FELT may utilize email to communicate with you from time to time.   By providing your email address to FELT, you are consenting to email as a communication medium between FELT and you.   Occasionally, you may be asked to verify your email address to assure the accuracy of our database.
OPT-OUT OPTION
You have the right to "opt-out" and request removal of your email address from our send list.   If you choose to opt-out, you must opt out for every email address you have provided to FELT, or you may inadvertently be sent an email to one of your email addresses that have not yet opted out.   You may opt out by selecting the opt-out option when providing personal information to FELT, by selecting the opt out option in reply to emails sent to you, or by emailing us via our CONTACT US page.
SUBMISSIONS TO US
If you send us an e-mail or submit and article, idea or proposal, please be advised that e-mail communications are not secure.   If you communicate with us in connection with a matter for which we do not already represent you, you should not send us confidential or sensitive information via e-mail because your communication will not be treated as privileged or confidential.   Any articles, feedback, information or materials submitted to Felt ("Submissions") shall be considered non-confidential by Felt.   By providing such Submissions to Felt, you agree that Felt shall have, at no charge, a non-exclusive, transferable, royalty free, worldwide right and license to copy, edit, use, display, modify and distribute such Submissions and other intellectual property rights in and to the Submissions. Felt shall be free to use and disseminate such Submissions, and the ideas contained in such Submissions, on an unrestricted basis for any purpose.   You acknowledge that you are responsible for the Submissions that you provide, and that you, not Felt have full responsibility for the Submissions, including their legality and copyright
PRIVACY POLICY
We do not collect any personally-identifying information from our visitors unless you request a subscription to any of our on-line publications.   At that time, we may collect your first and last names, company affiliation and title, street address, telephone and fax numbers, e-mail address, and web page URL.   We do not share, rent or sell any of this information about you to third-parties and use it only for the purpose for which it was submitted.   If you would like to unsubscribe to a subscription, review any of the personal information we have retained, or have any other questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at dlr@paynefears.com.
We do not send our users "cookies," which are programs designed to track web site visitors and monitor web surfing habits.   We do, however, log IP addresses for systems administration purposes to track a visitor's session, which gives us an idea of which parts of our site you are visiting.   We do not link IP addresses to any personally-identifying information.
GENERAL
We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or delete portions of these terms of use at any time.   In the event that we do so, we will notify you of any such change, modification, addition, or deletion by prominently posting notice of the any such change, modification, addition, or deletion on the FELT website.   These terms of use shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California and the laws of the United States, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of law.   You agree that any action at law or in equity arising out of or relating to these terms shall be filed only in the state or federal courts located in Orange County, California, and you hereby consent and submit to the personal jurisdiction of such courts for the purposes of litigating any such action.   If any provision of these terms of use shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from these terms of use and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions.
Help Center & FAQ
Support
Contact Us
Careers
Bike Sizing
Product Registration
Manuals
Returns
Tag us #FeltFamily so we can follow your adventures.Felt is a proud member of Groupe Rossignol.
Select your region:
CANADA  :  EUROPE
Sign up to get the latest on sales, new releases and more …
Sign Up for our Newsletter
© 2020 Felt Bicycles.
